<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="intro_heading_text">Hi There, </string>
    <string name="intro_body_text">Thanks for Using Tech Announce Classifier</string>
    Your daily announcement just became easier to read through\n\n
    <string name="tutorial_heading_text"><b>How The Application Works</b></string>
	<string name="tutorial_body_text"><b>To View Announcement in a Category</b> - Click on a category or List  to see group of
        announcements listed under it \n\n
	<b>To Save a Particular Category as Favorite</b> - Long Press on the Category, a notification pops up that says
        “The category has been Saved to Favorite”.\n
	    <i>View selected category list in the Favorites Tab.</i>\n\n
	<b>To De-Select a Favorites Category </b> - Long Press on the Category.
        <i>While in the Favorites Tab</i>,the notification appears on the screen.\n\n
	<b>To View Most Recent Announcement </b> - click on the category, the announcements in this list appears.
        <i>This is the current list on Tech Announce website</i>. \n\n
	<b>To Save an Announcement to Saved Pages </b> - Long press the announcement,
        either on the Tag Tab or Most Recent Announcement List till a notification pops up on the screen. \n
        <i> View Saved Announcement list in the Saved-Pages Tab.</i>\n\n
	<b>To Remove Saved Announcement</b> - Long Press on the announcement. \n
        <i>While on the Saved-Pages Tab, the notification appears.</i>\n</string>
    <string name="conclusion_heading_text"><u>Please Take Note</u></string>
    <string name="conclusion_body_text">You can only save announcement to Saved_pages if it is Accessible to the App\n\n
    All Announcements are retrieved Daily at <b>11:05AM</b> If an announcement is posted after this set time,
        it will not be accessible to Select to Saved Pages.\n\n
    The checker, identify items, on accessible on you local device.\n\n
    Announcement are stored for a week, then deleted. if the announcement is not saved.\n</string>




</resources>